1
00:00:23,160 --> 00:00:24,400
I wanna be your man

2
00:00:24,580 --> 00:00:25,810
Your lover and your friend

3
00:00:25,990 --> 00:00:27,220
I'm gonna love you true

4
00:00:27,400 --> 00:00:29,780
I wanna be the one who you come home to

5
00:00:29,870 --> 00:00:31,190
It was Friday night, the moon was bright

6
00:00:31,280 --> 00:00:31,860
And the band was tight

7
00:00:31,990 --> 00:00:34,110
And I was flyin' when I met you

8
00:00:35,430 --> 00:00:36,140
You didn't seem to mind

9
00:00:36,220 --> 00:00:37,550
Spending your time with this crazy guy

10
00:00:37,640 --> 00:00:39,750
Whose eyes were wide open for you

11
00:00:41,160 --> 00:00:42,400
For a time, we had it good

I did the best I could AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA

12
00:00:43,990 --> 00:00:45,400
Til I lost you on the way

13
00:00:46,810 --> 00:00:48,050
You stood up for yourself

14
00:00:48,220 --> 00:00:49,370
Had to put us on the shelf

15
00:00:49,640 --> 00:00:51,050
For another day

16
00:00:51,930 --> 00:00:53,690
And I'll find some peace

17
00:00:54,050 --> 00:00:55,370
This time I'll let you know

18
00:00:55,640 --> 00:00:56,340
we're gonna grow

19
00:00:56,690 --> 00:00:58,190
I'm gonna show you my heart

20
00:00:58,640 --> 00:00:59,250
And soul

21
00:00:59,690 --> 00:01:00,220
This time

22
00:01:00,400 --> 00:01:01,110
This time

23
00:01:01,460 --> 00:01:02,520
MY LOVE

24
00:01:26,340 --> 00:01:28,280
I'm feeling small when I make the call full of alcohol

25
00:01:28,460 --> 00:01:30,840
And then there's dead air on the phone with you

26
00:01:31,990 --> 00:01:34,460
With my disguise, I didn't realize when I was hurting

27
00:01:34,810 --> 00:01:36,490
That I was hurting you too

28
00:01:37,990 --> 00:01:38,870
So when I lost my way

29
00:01:39,050 --> 00:01:40,280
Couldn't think of what to say

30
00:01:40,460 --> 00:01:42,050
I watched us fall apart

31
00:01:43,280 --> 00:01:44,340
There's an opportunity

32
00:01:44,690 --> 00:01:45,710
It's here for you and me

33
00:01:46,190 --> 00:01:48,050
To make another start

34
00:01:48,220 --> 00:01:50,160
And I'll find some peace

35
00:01:50,520 --> 00:01:52,990
This time I'll let you know we're gonna grow

36
00:01:53,160 --> 00:01:54,750
I'm gonna show you my heart

37
00:01:55,110 --> 00:01:55,810
And soul

38
00:01:56,160 --> 00:01:56,780
This time

39
00:01:56,870 --> 00:01:57,580
This time

40
00:01:57,930 --> 00:01:58,990
My love

41
00:02:29,690 --> 00:02:31,110
I need to find a way

42
00:02:32,340 --> 00:02:34,460
I need to follow through

43
00:02:35,160 --> 00:02:37,280
I need to find the faith

44
00:02:37,990 --> 00:02:41,520
To help us make it Through

45
00:02:41,690 --> 00:02:44,520
Make it through
